seabreeze.com.au 2019-03-18

# Privacy Policy

Welcome! Read on how Seabreeze.com.au treats your personal information, along with ways to control your preferences and settings. 

**Seabreeze.com.au is committed to gaining & retaining your trust.**

**Seabreeze.com.au takes your privacy seriously!**

**General**

Seabreeze.com.au collects personal information when you register with Seabreeze.com.au, when you use Seabreeze.com.au products or services, when you visit Seabreeze.com.au pages or the pages of certain Seabreeze.com.au partners, and when you enter promotions or competitions. Seabreeze.com.au may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.

When you register we may ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, postcode, occupation, industry, and personal interests. For some products and services we might also ask for your address.

Seabreeze.com.au collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including information about your use of services that we offer.

Seabreeze.com.au automatically receives and records information from your computer and browser, including your IP address, Seabreeze.com.au cookie information, software and hardware attributes, and the page you request.

Seabreeze.com.au uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

**Information Sharing & Disclosure**

Seabreeze.com.au does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Seabreeze.com.au under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help Seabreeze.com.au communicate with you about offers from Seabreeze.com.au and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.

We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process (such as law enforcement requests), or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

We believe it is necessary to view & share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Seabreeze.com.au's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

We transfer information about you if Seabreeze.com.au is acquired by or merged with another company.

Seabreeze.com.au may display targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click targeted ads meet the targeting criteria—for example, men ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area.

Seabreeze.com.au does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad.

**Cookies & Similar Technologies**

Seabreeze.com.au may set and access Seabreeze.com.au cookies on your computer. We may also set and access device identifiers which could include IP address, user agent information (browser version, OS type and version), and device provided identifiers. Once you log into Seabreeze.com.au on your device, Seabreeze.com.au may recognize your device to provide you with a personalized experience, independent of your device settings.

Seabreeze.com.au lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies and device identifiers is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Seabreeze.com.au's cookies.

**Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences**

You can edit your Seabreeze.com.au Account Information, including your notification preferences, at any time. You can also modify information you have provided to Seabreeze.com.au through the Seabreeze.com.au products or services you may use.

We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the Seabreeze.com.au service, such as service announcements, administrative messages that are considered part of your Seabreeze.com.au account, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them. We also reserve the right to send you Seabreeze.com.au Digests / Newsletters, however should you not enjoy them you can easily opt out via the Notifactions tab on your Member Profile page.

**Confidentiality & Security**

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

**Credit Card Details**

Seabreeze.com.au only retains these for less than the time it takes to send to our payment provider, whereupon they are discarded.   Your credit card number is not stored by Seabreeze except for the duration of the transaction.

You can edit & adjust your newsletter / marketting preferences via the Members / My Profile link, when you are logged in.

Any queries or questions?  Visit the Contact link at the bottom of the page to get in contact.
